[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wichita, a major aircraft manufacturing hub and cultural center, is the capital of Kansas.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is it not recommended to be keep raccoons as pets?", "correct_answer": "They can be aggressive.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have and intense odor.", "Their fur promotes allergies.", "They transmit many diseases."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long are the intestines of an average adult? (large and small)", "correct_answer": "approx 8-9 meters (26-29.5 feet)", "incorrect_answers": ["approx 1-2 meters (3-6.5 feet)", "approx 19-20 meters (62-65 feet)", "approx 15-16 meters (49-52.5 feet)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following Leonardo DiCaprio movies did Martin Scorsese NOT direct?", "correct_answer": "Catch Me If You Can", "incorrect_answers": ["The Aviator", "The Departed", "Gangs of New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is soap?", "correct_answer": "a base with a bitter taste", "incorrect_answers": ["an acid with a sour taste", "an acid with a bitter taste", "a base with a sour taste"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "\u201cAppointing your grandmother to office for the good of the party\u201d is the definition of which of these words in the satirical book by Ambrose Bierce The Devils Dictionary?", "correct_answer": "Nepotism", "incorrect_answers": ["Favoritism", "Humanitarianism", "Socialism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country is involved together with the US in the plot of the 1995 movie Crimson Tide?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["North Korea", "Cuba", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 2006 movie that starred these actors voices: Paul Newman, Owen Wilson and Bonnie Hunt.", "correct_answer": "Cars", "incorrect_answers": ["Lion King", "Finding Nemo", "The Incredibles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character did Jennifer Aniston voice in the 1998 animated TV series Hercules?", "correct_answer": "Galatea", "incorrect_answers": ["Calliope", "Aphrodite", "Hera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Chinatown, Hollis I. Mulwray owned the water department.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tusks of mature elephants stop growing when the animal reaches a certain age.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these schemes from the 2004 movie Oceans Twelve requires a trained cat to be carried out?", "correct_answer": "Hell in a Handbasket", "incorrect_answers": ["Bakers Dozen", "Crazy Larry", "Soft Shoulder"]}]